calumetphoto.co.uk 2017-04-20

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

### Information We Collect:

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the CalPhoto.co.uk website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

Name  
Address  
Email address  
Phone number  
(additional fields on the form)

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:

Name  
Address  
Phone Number  
(additional fields on the form)

### Usage of Information:

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order and confirm you are happy with your transaction.

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

### Use of Cookies

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, and keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third Party Links

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by going to the My Account section of calphoto.co.uk

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

### Newsletters

If you have subscribed to our newsletter, you can unsubscribe at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link in each email

If you subscribe to our newsletter, your email address will be used for marketing purposes unless you choose to unsubscribe. Unsubscribing is possible at any time and incurs no charges to you.

If you have signed up for our newsletter we will use the data that you have given us when you register only for the purposes of sending you our newsletter. We do not disclose your data to any third parties except the companies we have partnered with to facilitate the technical aspects of sending our newsletters. In these cases the amount of data transferred is limited to the minimum necessary.

### Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

### How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 0333 003 5000, send us an email at [webmaster@calphoto.co.uk](mailto:webmaster@calphoto.co.uk) or mail us at:

Calumet Photographic  
Bradbourne Drive  
Tilbrook  
Milton Keynes  
MK7 8AJ
